condecosoftware.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy | Condeco Software

### What information do we collect?

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information.

  * Information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including Names, Job Title, Company Name, Email Address, Telephone Number, Country, Interests).
  * Any other information that you choose to send to us.

### Cookies

To make full use of the personalised features on the website, your computer, tablet or mobile phone will need to accept cookies, as we can only provide you with certain personalised features of this website by using them.

Our cookies don’t store sensitive information such as your name, address: they simply hold the ‘key’ that, once you’re signed in, is associated with this information. However, if you’d prefer to restrict, block or delete cookies from our website, or any other website, you can use your browser to do this. Each browser is different, so check the ‘Help’ menu of your particular browser (or your mobile phone’s handset manual) to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

#### Cookies References

Cookie | Purpose | Provider  
---|---|---  
__ar*, __adroll | AdRoll ‘remarketing cookie’, used to provide interest-based advertisements to show our ads on other websites. | Adroll  
__cfduid* | Used to identify individual clients behind a shared IP address and apply security settings on a per-client basis. | Cloudflare  
__distillery, muxData, wistia-* | Cookies set by wistia for its video player and video behaviour. | Wistia  
__gads, DSID, IDE, bdfSurf | These cookies set by a third party (DoubleClick) and are used for serving targeted advertisements that are relevant to you across the web. Targeted advertisements may be displayed to you based on your previous visits to this website. For more information, please visit [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) – Disabling steps go here – [adssettings.google.com ](https://adssettings.google.com/) | Google – DoubleClick  
__hs*, hubspotutk, hsPagesViewedThisSession, hsfirstvisit, messagesUtk, __hluid, __cfduid | Cookies set by HubSpot to keep track of visitors on Condeco. | HubSpot  
__utm* | Google Analytics non-personally identifiable information used for website analytics. | Google  
_Condecopolicy, visited | Allows Condeco to track user acceptance of our cookie policy, user tracking, for serving a better experience to our users. | Condeco Software  
_ga, _gid | Google Analytics cookie, used to distinguish users. | Google  
_hj* | Hotjar cookie. This cookie is set to understand visitor interactions and analytics. | Hotjar  
_mp_* | These cookies are used to analyze activity on our website and application in order to improve the user experience. This information is shared with Mixpanel. | Mixpanel  
_uetsid, MUIDB, MUID | Microsoft Bing Ads Universal Event Tracking (UET) tracking cookie. | Microsoft  
_vwo_uuid | This cookie generates a unique ID for every visitor and is used for the report segmentation feature in VWO. | VWO  
  
#### Specific Cookie descriptions

##### HubSpot

Our Site also employs HubSpot, which collects personal identifying information by using javascript and cookies to help us analyze how visitors use the Site. HubSpot’s products help us to identify Site visitors, analyze email campaigns, track Site contact forms and monitor Google AdWords click through. Anonymous visitor tracking information may be shared with other HubSpot customers. For more information about HubSpot cookies, please visit <https://knowledge.hubspot.com/articles/kcs_article/account/hubspot-cookie-security-and-privacy>

##### HotJar

Hotjar is an analytics and feedback tool that we use to understand how our website is used and improve usability. Hotjar sets cookies to help us track behaviour across pages and to control visitor polls. The cookies carry no personally identifiable information. For more information on HotJar Cookies please visit: <https://help.hotjar.com/hc/en-us/articles/115011789248-Hotjar-Cookies>

##### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: <https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage>

#### 3rd party tags

We use tags from 3rd party suppliers dedicated to helping us improve the relevance of our advertising banners, both on our website and across the web where we have advertisements on other websites. Our advertising policy is designed to give you the most relevant adverts possible. A tag is simply a way for us to identify if a specific page was viewed by a customer and use that information to form a more accurate advertising strategy.

#### What is a Cookie and how to manage them

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We use session cookies on the website. Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. We will use the session cookies for the following purposes: To prevent accidental contact form resubmissions.

Each browser is different, so check the ‘Help’ menu of your particular browser (or your mobile phone’s handset manual) to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking Tools, Internet Options, Privacy, and selecting Block all cookies using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.

### Using your personal information

Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information for the following purposes.

  * To enable your use of the services available on the website.
  * To send to you marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications).
  * To deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website.

### Disclosures

We may disclose information about you to any of our employees and subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

All our subcontractors are compliant with personal data protection laws. Condeco has in place legally binding agreements with their subcontractors. Nevertheless, Condeco remains responsible for the processing of personal data.

In addition, we may disclose your personal information in the following circumstances.

  * To the extent that we are required to disclose information by law.
  * In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings.
  * In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk).

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

### Security of your personal information

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Condeco is certified according to ISO 27001:2013 and CSA STAR standards: we will store all the personal information you provide on our certified IT infrastructure.

Moreover, data at rest in our systems and in transit over the Internet are always encrypted.

### Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

### Your rights

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information will be subject to the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a solicitor or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current address).

In particular, you may raise a request (DSAR – Data Subject Access Request) sending a e-mail at the following address [privacy@condecosoftware.com](mailto:privacy@condecosoftware.com) and specifying the code of your specific request as follows:

  * access (DSAR-01)
  * rectification (DSAR-02)
  * erasure (DSAR-03)
  * restriction of processing (DSAR-04)
  * data portability (DSAR-05)
  * objection to profiling (DSAR-06)

We remind you that, even if you have explicitly opted-in to receive our communications, you may instruct us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes by email at any time

### Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

### GDPR Policy

If you are interested to view our GDPR Policy, you may [download it here](https://2ddbbz2b4d271ihlk62v0fgx-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/General-Data-Protection-Policy.pdf).

### Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please write to our Data Protection Officer by email or by post to the following address:

**Graham Cole**  
Information Security Officer (DPO)  
Condeco Group  
8th Floor, Exchange Tower  
2 Harbour Exchange Square  
London  
E14 9GE  
United Kingdom

**T** +44 (0)20 7001 2083  
**E** [privacy@condecosoftware.com](mailto:privacy@condecosoftware.com)
